## MD. ROBEUL ISLAM

Address: House: 17/1/B, Moddho Paik Para, Darus Salam, Dhaka

Primary Mobile No: 01922088046 Emergency Contact No: 01725930131 Primary Email: robeulcse1@gmail.com Alternate Email: robicse8@gmail.com



### **Career Objective:**

To work with a progressive organization, where I can utilize my skills. And look forward for overall growth of itself as well as of its supporting elements ensuring a wonderful work environment and work hard to achieve the corporate targets and goals

## **Career Summary:**

I have experienced in Laravel 7, CodeIgniter 4, Bootstrap, React JS, MySQL 5.7+, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, HTML5, CSS3, Restful API,Version Control System (GIT) And also have more than 4-year experience in developing & maintenance software development and web-based platforms.

#### **Special Qualification:**

B.Sc. in Computer Science and Engineering(CSE)

## **Employment History:**

Total Year of Experience: 6 yrs

#### 1. Software Engineering( 1.7 yrs )

(September, 2020 - Continuing)

#### Star IT Ltd.

5th Floor (Lift Button-4), BBTOA Building, 9 No South

#### Area of Expertise

Programmer/ Software Engineer (1.4 yrs)

#### **Duties/Responsibilities**

Work multi purpose project

## 2. Web Developer( 1 yr )

(February, 2019 - February, 2020)

#### Star IT Ltd.

5th Floor (Lift Button-4), BBTOA Building, 9 No South, Mirpur Road, Dhaka 1207

### Area of Expertise

Ecommerce (0.3 yr), Software Development (0.3 yr), Web Developer/ Web Designer (0.3 yr)

### **Duties/Responsibilities**

Work multi purpose project

#### 3. Web Developer( 3.2 yrs )

(October, 2015 - January, 2019)

#### Windmill InfoTech Ltd

West Wind Point | 2nd Floor 89/4 & 89/5 | North Badda, Dhaka-1212

## **Area of Expertise**

Programmer/ Software Engineer ( 1.6 yrs ), Web Developer/ Web Designer ( 1.6 yrs )

### **Duties/Responsibilities**

Work with attention and dynamically with team leader and team members.

## **Academic Qualification:**

<b>Exam Title</b>	Concentration/Major	ation/Major Institute		Pas.Year	Duration	
B. Sc in CSE	Computer Science & Engineering	Dhaka International University	CGPA:3.85 out of 4	2014	2010-2014	
HSC	Science	ence Ahmedpur College-2		2009	2007-2009	
SSC	Science	Boro Baria High School	CGPA:4.38 out of 5	2007	2001-2007	

#### **Training Summary:**

Training Title	Topic	Institute	Country	Location	Year	Duration
IT Projects & Process	How to develop a project into a good project?	Windmill Infotech Limited	Bangladesh	Cha- 73/2, Progoti Shoroni, North Badda Dhaka- 1212	2015	16-06- 2015
CodeIgniter	PHP Framework	BASIS	Bangladesh	kawran Bazar Branch	2014	4 Month

# **Professional Qualification:**

Certification	Institute	Location	From	То
Web Developer	Windmill Infotech Limited	West Wind Point, 2nd Floor 89/4 & 89/5, Dhaka 1212	October 1, 2015	January 31, 2019

## **Career and Application Information:**

Looking For : Entry Level Job
Available For : Full Time
Present Salary : Tk. 35000
Expected Salary : Tk. 40000

Preferred Job Category : IT/Telecommunication
Preferred District : Dhaka, Rajshahi

Preferred Organization Types : Telecommunication, Software Company, IT Enabled Service, E-commerce

## **Specialization:**

Fields of Specialization	Description
<ul> <li>MySQL</li> <li>PHP</li> <li>JavaScript</li> <li>CodeIgniter</li> <li>Ajax</li> <li>jQuery</li> <li>Laravel Framework</li> </ul>	Currently, I have worked the following project. Laravel Framework:  1.http://bbazar.com.bd (ecommerce site) 2.https://bengalfish.com.bd (ecommerce site) 3.http://boibichitraerp.xyz/login (Inventory, HRM, Accounting) 4.http://fabriclagbe.com (Fabric, Bid, Sale And Commission) 5.https://knoprotec.com (ecommerce site) 6.https://priyojon.care (Hospital Management Application) 7.https://taxman.com.bd (Tax Submit) 8.https://iboiit.com (Referral System) 9.http://dreamzon.store (POS System) 10.http://simco.com.bd/accounts (Stock Management Software)

11.https://www.rideox.com (Website)

12.http://shimueps-accounts.com (Accounting and Inventory)

13.https://dailyservice.net (Service Oriented)

CodeIgniter Framework:

1. http://bpelbdsoft.com/login (Inventory and Manufacturer Software)

2.https://binnakuri.com (ecommerce site)

3.http://www.charcoalboard.com (HR, Leave, Attendance And Salary)

# **Extra Curricular Activities:**

Coding and Internet browsing

## **Language Proficiency:**

Language	Reading	Writing	Speaking	
English	High	Medium	Medium	
Bangla	High	High	High	

#### **Personal Details:**

Father's Name : Md. Alkas Ali

Mother's Name : Mst. Feroza Khatun
Date of Birth : December 2, 1992

Gender : Male
Marital Status : Married
Nationality : Bangladeshi
National Id No. : 5095433560

Religion : Islam

Permanent Address : Luxmipur, Natore Sadar, Natore Sadar, Natore 6400

Current Location : Dhaka